Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Anti-Communism and Subversive Activities, 1928-1975; (154 boxes)
  - Subversive - "Guerrilla Warfare Advocates in the United States" - Report., 1968 (Folder 11, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Subversive Influence on Certain Industrial Plants in Eastern Pa" - Hearings, October 13, 18, 1954 (Folder 12, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Subversive Infiltration of radio, television, and the entertainment industry" - Hearings, March 20, 26, April 23, May 20, 1952 (Folder 13, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Hearings relating to HR 15262, HR 15626, HR 15649, HR 16613, HR 16757, HR 15018, HR 15092, HR 15229, HR 1572, HR 15336, and HR 15828 Amending the subversive activities control act of 1950" - Hearings. Part 1 and Part 2., 1968 (Folder 14, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Communist Commitment to force and violence" - Report, March 2, 1968 (Folder 15, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Never Printed - subversive involvement and disruption of 1968 - Democrat party national convention" Part 1 (Folder 16, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Defense Facilities and industrial security act of 1968" (Folder 17, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Subversive Involvement in Disruption of 1968 - Democratic Party National Convention" Part 1 - Hearings (Folder 18, Box 124)
  - Subversive - "Subversive Involvement in Disruption of 1968 - Democratic Party National Convention" Part 2 - Hearings (Folder 1, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Subversive Involvement in Disruption of 1968, Democratic Party National Convention" Part 3 - Hearings, December 4, 5 1968 (Folder 2, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union" - Hearings, June 19, 1968 (Folder 3, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Hearings Relating to HR 959, Amending the Internal Security Act of 1950 (obstruction of armed forces)" - Hearings, 1969 (Folder 4, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "SDS Plans for America's High School" - Report, 1969 (Folder 5, Box 125)
    Committee on Internal Security, Students for a Democratic Society
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 1-A (George Washington University), 1969 (Folder 7, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society " Part 1-B (Georgetown University), 1969 (Folder 8, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 2 (Kent State University), 1969 (Folder 9, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 3-A (George Washington University), 1969 (Folder 10, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 3-B (George Washington University), 1969 (Folder 11, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 4 (The American University), 1969 (Folder 12, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 5 (University of Chicago; communist party efforts with regard to SDS), 1969 (Folder 13, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 6-A (Columbus, Ohio, High Schools), 1970 (Folder 14, Box 125)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 6-B (Akron, Ohio; Detroit, Michigan; Pittsburgh, PA), 1970 (Folder 1, Box 126)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 7-A (Return of Prisoners of War and Data Concerning Camera News, Inc.,"Newsreel"), 1969 (Folder 2, Box 126)
  - Subversive - "Investigation of Students for a Democratic Society" Part 7-B (SDS activities at Fort Dix N.J; Washington D.C. and Chicago, Ill.), 1969 (Folder 3, Box 126)
  - Subversive - "Defense Facilities and Industrial Security Act of 1970" - Report - (5 copies) (Folder 4, Box 126)
    Committee on Internal Security, Ichord, National Security
  - Subversive - "Federal Governments Handling of Soviet and Communist bloc Defectors" - Hearings, 1987 (Folder 5, Box 126)
    Committee on Governmental Affairs, Defectors, Soviet Union, Soviet Bloc
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1971-1972 (Folder 6, Box 126)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1970-1971 (Folder 7, Box 126)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1968 - 1969 (Folder 8, Box 126)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board: court cases, 1960-1971 (Folder 1, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board court cases, 1971-1972 (Folder 2, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1971-1972 (Folder 3, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1964 (Folder 4, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1970s (Folder 5, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1968-1971 (Folder 6, Box 127)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1964 - 1965 (Folder 1, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1965 (Folder 2, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases, 1965 (Folder 3, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (Davis, Lightfoot, Hall, Kushner), 1963 (Folder 4, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (Albertson, Friedlander, Patterson, Tormey), 1962 (Folder 5, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (L.J. Libson), 1964 (Folder 6, Box 128)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (Stanford, Dobbs, Taylor, Gabow), 1963 (Folder 1, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (Potash), 1963 (Folder 2, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board-court cases (Meyers, Nabrid, Edelman), 1963 (Folder 3, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1967-1973 (Folder 4, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1967-1972 (Folder 5, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1967-1973 (Folder 6, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1967-1973 (Folder 7, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1948-1949 (Folder 8, Box 129)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1950-1956 (Folder 1, Box 130)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1954-1966 (Folder 2, Box 130)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1966-1968 (Folder 3, Box 130)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1968-1969 (Folder 4, Box 130)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1969-1971 (Folder 5, Box 130)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, hearings, 1971-1972 (Folder 6, Box 130)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1956-1979 (Folder 1, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1969-1987 (Folder 2, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1951-1982 (Folder 3, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1951-1982 (Folder 4, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1957-1972 (Folder 5, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1970-1971 (Folder 6, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1966 (Folder 7, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1967-1972 (Folder 8, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1967-1973 (Folder 9, Box 131)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1967-1973 (Folder 1, Box 132)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1950-1973 (Folder 2, Box 132)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board], 1950-1973 (Folder 3, Box 132)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board] [Otepka], 1968-1973 (Folder 4, Box 132)
  - SACB [Subversive Activities Control Board] [Otepka], 1969-1972 (Folder 5, Box 132)
  - Subversive organizations, 1950s (Folder 6, Box 132)
  - Law Suits-organizations, 1971-1977 (Folder 7, Box 132)
    CIA, ITT
  - Sullivan, William C., 1960-1979 (Folder 8, Box 132)
    Espionage, FBI, Soviet Union, Subversive Activities
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 9, Box 132)
    Court Decisions, Newspaper Clippings
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950-1988 (Folder 2, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950-1988 (Folder 3, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1955-1958 (Folder 4, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 5, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 6, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 7, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 8, Box 133)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 134)
  - Supreme Court, 1957 (Folder 2, Box 134)
  - Supreme Court, 1955-1969 (Folder 3, Box 134)
  - Supreme Court - County of Albany, 1949 (Folder 4, Box 134)
  - SWAT-emergency response teams, 1975-1982 (Folder 5, Box 134)
  - SWP-suit (FBI, CIA, etc.): 73 Civ. 3160, 1975-1986 (Folder 6, Box 134)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Socialist Workers' Party
  - SWP [Socialist Workers Party], 1971-1978 (Folder 7, Box 134)
    Socialist Workers Party
  - SWP-YSA, 1973-1977 (Folder 8, Box 134)
    Socialist Workers Party, Young Socialist Alliance
  - SWP and YSA, 1969-1971 (Folder 9, Box 134)
  - SWP-YSA, 1971-1979 (Folder 1, Box 135)
  - Szulc, Tad, 1975 (Folder 2, Box 135)
    Newspaper Column, Nonfiction
  - Talamente, Olga, 1975-1977 (Folder 3, Box 135)
    Argentine Commission for Human Rights
  - Taps-attorney general's on the Justice Department, 1971-1973 (Folder 4, Box 135)
    Wiretapping
  - Taylor, Telford-grad inquest, 1953-1956 (Folder 5, Box 135)
    Loyalty Oaths, McCarthy
  - Teacher No. 2, 1950s (Folder 6, Box 135)
    Anti-Communism, Teacher Suspensions
  - Teachers No. 2, 1950s (Folder 7, Box 135)
  - Teachers No. 2, 1953 (Folder 8, Box 135)
  - Tech [Technological] intelligence, 1974-1978 (Folder 9, Box 135)
    CIA, Spy Satellites
  - Television, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 136)
    Anti-Communism, Counterattack, Red Channels
  - Television, 1950s (Folder 2, Box 136)
  - Terror-US government, 1973-1991 (Folder 3, Box 136)
    National Security, Terrorism
  - Terror-US government, 1973-1991 (Folder 4, Box 136)
  - Terror-USSR etc. doctrine, 1970-1978 (Folder 5, Box 136)
    Transnational Terrorism, Soviet Union
  - Terrorism, 1970-1994 (Folder 6, Box 136)
    Libya, National Security, Terrorism
  - Terrorism, 1970-1994 (Folder 7, Box 136)
    Bombing, Libya, Sudan, World Trade Center
  - Terrorism, 1972-1995 (Folder 8, Box 136)
    Anti-American, IRA, Israel, Lebanon, Palestine
  - Terrorism, 1970-1989 (Folder 9, Box 136)
    Hezbollah, Israel, National Security, PLO
  - Terrorism, 1970-1985 (Folder 1, Box 137)
    Bombing, Hijacking, PLO
  - Terrorism, 1971-1985 (Folder 2, Box 137)
    Bombing, Hijacking, Hostages, Iran
  - Terrorism-business, 1974-1984 (Folder 3, Box 137)
    Body Guards, Corporate Targets, Kidnapping
  - Terrorism-definition, 1974-1986 (Folder 4, Box 137)
  - Terrorism-international, 1975-1978 (Folder 5, Box 137)
  - Terrorism-international, 1975-1978 (Folder 6, Box 137)
  - Terrorism-international, 1975-1978 (Folder 7, Box 137)
  - Terrorist - danger, 1975-1976 (Folder 8, Box 137)
    Act to Combat Terrorism
  - Testimony - Terrorism, 1975 (Folder 9, Box 137)
    Terrorist Threat
  - Theater, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1950s (Folder 2, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1951 (Folder 3, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1952 (Folder 4, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1953 (Folder 5, Box 138)
  - Theater-folk etc., 1959-1986 (Folder 6, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1949 - 1950 (Folder 7, Box 138)
  - Theater, 1950 (Folder 1, Box 139)
  - The American Legion Firing Line by the National Americanism Commission, 1957-1962 (Folder 2, Box 139)
    Firing Line
  - The Fund for Open Information and Accountability Inc., 1975-1984 (Folder 3, Box 139)
    FOIA
  - Theoretical Aspects of the Negro Question in the United States, 1959 (Folder 4, Box 139)
    Communist Party, USA
  - They Call It Free Enterprise - but...", 1948 (Folder 5, Box 139)
    Anti-American, Religion
  - Thomas Jefferson: Selections form his Writings, 1943 (Folder 6, Box 139)
    Jefferson, Thomas
  - The Threat of Red Sabotage, 1950 (Folder 7, Box 139)
    Communism, Sabotage
  - Timothy Leary, 1966-1986 (Folder 8, Box 139)
    Leary, Timothy
  - Today's World, 1946-1947 (Folder 9, Box 139)
  - Trade - Boycotts, 1950s (Folder 10, Box 139)
    Boycott, Communist Industry
  - Trade - Boycotts, 1950s (Folder 11, Box 139)
  - Trade - Boycotts, 1950s (Folder 12, Box 139)
  - Transcripts dispersal, 1971-1973 (Folder 13, Box 139)
    McNamara, Notes, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Turco, Arthur F. Jr. (Panthers-Baltimore), 1970-1971 (Folder 1, Box 140)
    Racism, Trials
  - Turk-Armenian, 1979-1982 (Folder 2, Box 140)
    Turkey, Armenia, Terrorism
  - UE [United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers], 1948-1949 (Folder 3, Box 140)
    Labor, Newspaper Clippings
  - UE [United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers], 1948-1949 (Folder 4, Box 140)
  - VFW, 1955-1960 (Folder 5, Box 140)
    Veterans of Foreign Wars
  - The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, May 5, 1955 (Folder 6, Box 140)
    American Legion, Human Rights, UNESCO, United Nations
  - University, 1950-1953 (Folder 7, Box 140)
    Court Decisions, Loyalty Oaths, Supreme Court
  - UNRRA, 1945-1948 (Folder 8, Box 140)
    United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration
  - USAC, 1960s (Folder 9, Box 140)
    US Anti-Communist Congress, Inc.
  - USACC, 1969-1979 (Folder 10, Box 140)
  - US agent exposure, 1975-1989 (Folder 11, Box 140)
    CIA, KGB
  - USAF Special Operations School, 1968-1969 (Folder 12, Box 140)
    Sabotage, Subversive Activities
  - U.S. court of Appeals: on petition for review of order of the Subversive Activities Control Board, 1963 (Folder 1, Box 141)
  - US foreign policy and Eastern Europe: a private study, 1960 (Folder 2, Box 141)
    Committee on Foreign Relations
  - US miscellaneous groups, 1975-1978 (Folder 3, Box 141)
    Subversive Activities
  - USSR subversion, 1950s (Folder 4, Box 141)
    Soviet Union, Subversive Activities
  - U-2, 1960-1961 (Folder 5, Box 141)
    Lockheed U-2, Dragon Lady, Spy Plane
  - U-2, 1960-1961 (Folder 6, Box 141)
  - VB (Venceremos Brigade), 1969-1981 (Folder 7, Box 141)
    Cuba, Intelligence
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1955-1960 (Folder 8, Box 141)
    Anti-Communism, Propaganda, Sovereignty
  - [Veterans Organizations], 1969 (Folder 9, Box 141)
    Anti-War
  - Veterans ([Joseph P.] Polowsky-Elbe River, etc.), 1950s (Folder 10, Box 141)
    Anti-Communism, GI's, Propaganda
  - V.F.W. American Security Reporter, December 1972 (Folder 11, Box 141)
    Anti-Communism, National Security, Veterans of Foreign Wars
  - The Vietnam Dilemma, 1967 (Folder 12, Box 141)
    Anti-War, Vietnam
  - Vietnam demonstrations, 1971 (Folder 13, Box 141)
  - Vietnam demonstrations, 1971 (Folder 1, Box 142)
  - Vietnam demonstrations, 1971 (Folder 2, Box 142)
  - Vietnam demonstrations, 1971 (Folder 3, Box 142)
  - Vietnam, 1969-1973 (Folder 4, Box 142)
  - Vietnam, 1969-1973 (Folder 5, Box 142)
  - Vietnam, 1970-1973 (Folder 6, Box 142)
  - Vietnam, 1970-1973 (Folder 7, Box 142)
  - Vietnam, 1955-1989 (Folder 8, Box 142)
  - Vietnam Draft US, 1969 (Folder 9, Box 142)
    Draft, Anti-War, Vietnam
  - Vietnam Draft US, 1968-1971 (Folder 1, Box 143)
  - Vietnam Draft US, 1955-1982 (Folder 2, Box 143)
  - Vietnam Draft US, 1967-1972 (Folder 3, Box 143)
  - Viet War Protests, 1967-1982 (Folder 4, Box 143)
    Vietnam Demonstrations
  - Viet War Protests, 1967-1982 (Folder 5, Box 143)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1965-1992 (Folder 6, Box 143)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1961-1993 (Folder 7, Box 143)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1962-1991 (Folder 1, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1962-1991 (Folder 2, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1969-1988 (Folder 3, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1964-1978 (Folder 4, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1964-1978 (Folder 5, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1965-1979 (Folder 6, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1968-1969 (Folder 7, Box 144)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1965-1969 (Folder 1, Box 145)
  - Vietnam War protests, 1965-1969 (Folder 2, Box 145)
  - Vietnam veterans against the war, 1970-1971 (Folder 3, Box 145)
  - Voice From The Mother Country, ca. 1970 (Folder 4, Box 145)
    Newspaper, Washington, D.C.
  - VVAW, 1970s (Folder 5, Box 145)
    Vietnam Veterans Against the War
  - VVAW, 1970s (Folder 6, Box 145)
  - Erica Wallach report, 1940-1960 (Folder 7, Box 145)
    Noel Field, Alger Hiss, Soviet Union, Ukraine
  - Erica Wallach report, 1940-1960 (Folder 8, Box 145)
  - Wallach, Erica (and Noel Field), 1958-1993 (Folder 9, Box 145)
  - Walter, Francis E. (Folder 1, Box 146)
    Congress, Correspondence, House Un-American Activities Committee
  - Walter, Francis E. "Mesa Sertoma Club", 1961 (Folder 2, Box 146)
    Draft of Speech
  - Walter, Francis E. "Willow Grove Naval Air Station", 1961 (Folder 3, Box 146)
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Disabled American Veterans Convention", 1961 (Folder 4, Box 146)
    Veterans
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Riveria Country Club", 1961 (Folder 5, Box 146)
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Operation Alert", 1961 (Folder 6, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, North Carolina, Operation Alert
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Know Your America Week", 1961 (Folder 7, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Rough Draft
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "American Jewish League Against Communism", 1962 (Folder 8, Box 146)
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Red China", ca. 1961 (Folder 9, Box 146)
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "The Story of W.H. 'Ping' Ferry", ca. 1961 (Folder 10, Box 146)
    W. H. 'Ping' Ferry, Fund for the Republic
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Northampton Area Chamber of Commerce Annual Dinner", 1961 (Folder 11, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, National Security
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Draft of Chairman's Speech for Catholic War Veterans", 1961 (Folder 12, Box 146)
    Religion, War Veterans
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Alabama American State Convention", 1961 (Folder 13, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Political Affairs
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speech "Ping and the Fund for the Republic", ca. 1961 (Folder 14, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Fund for the Republics
  - Walter, Francis E., 1962 (Folder 15, Box 146)
    Congressional Records
  - Walter, Francis E.'s speeches, 1961 (Folder 16, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Committee on Un-American Activities, Veterans
  - Walter speeches (extras), 1959-1962 (Folder 17, Box 146)
    Congressional Records, Committee on Un-American Activities
  - Walter speeches (extras), 1959-1962 (Folder 18, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Committee on Un-American Activities, Sons of America, Veterans
  - Walter speeches etc.: not reproduced, 1961-1963 (Folder 19, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, Committee on Un-American Activities
  - Walter speeches (extras), 1961-1962 (Folder 20, Box 146)
    Anti-Communism, China, National Security, United Nations
  - Walter speeches: Mimeo'd, CR, etc., 1957-1962 (Folder 1, Box 147)
    Anti-Communism, China, National Security, Veterans
  - Walter speeches: Mimeo'd, CR, etc., 1961-1962 (Folder 2, Box 147)
  - Walter speeches: Mimeo'd, CR etc., 1959-1963 (Folder 3, Box 147)
  - Rep. Walter Speech "Disciplining Our Right to Know", 1969-1986 (Folder 4, Box 147)
  - War crimes inquiry, 1970-1971 (Folder 5, Box 147)
    Laos, Vietnam, Veterans
  - Washington [DC] metropolitan area, 1974-1990 (Folder 6, Box 147)
    Montgomery City, Prince George's County, Virginia
  - Washington Peace Center Newsletter, ca.1971 (Folder 7, Box 147)
    Washington Peace Center
  - Washington Post apology to McNamara, 1963 (Folder 8, Box 147)
    Committee on Un-American Activities, McCarthy, McNamara, Washington Post
  - Washington Report, 1962 (Folder 9, Box 147)
  - Washington Report, 1963 (Folder 10, Box 147)
  - Washington Report, 1964 (Folder 11, Box 147)
  - Washington Report, 1965 (Folder 12, Box 147)
  - Washington Report, 1966 (Folder 13, Box 147)
  - Washington Report, 1967 (Folder 1, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1968 (Folder 2, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1969 (Folder 3, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1970 (Folder 4, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1971 (Folder 5, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1972 (Folder 6, Box 148)
  - Washington Report, 1973 (Folder 7, Box 148)
  - Washington Report of the Air-broadcast highlights, 1972 (Folder 8, Box 148)
    Radio Free Americas
  - Watergate and CIA-FBI, 1974 (Folder 9, Box 148)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Watergate
  - Weatherman, 1969-1974 (Folder 10, Box 148)
    Offshoot Organization of Students for a Democratic Society
  - Welch, Richard S., 1975-1976 (Folder 11, Box 148)
  - West Germany, 1968-1991 (Folder 1, Box 149)
    Germany, Information Digest
  - Whistle blowing, 1969-1984 (Folder 2, Box 149)
  - White [Hayden] v. Edward Davis, 1975 (Folder 3, Box 149)
    Illegal Surveillance
  - Willis speeches plus remarks drafts, 1963-1965 (Folder 4, Box 149)
  - Willis speeches plus remarks drafts, 1963-1964 (Folder 5, Box 149)
  - Willis speeches plus remarks drafts, 1964-1968 (Folder 6, Box 149)
    Anti-Communism, Cold War, Committee on Un-American Activities
  - Willis speeches plus remarks drafts, 1963-1968 (Folder 7, Box 149)
    Anti-Communism, Committee on Un-American Activities, Ku Klux Klan
  - Willis [Edwin E.] speeches Mimeo, C.R., etc., 1964-1968 (Folder 8, Box 149)
  - Willis [Edwin E.] speeches Mimeo, C.R., etc., 1964-1968 (Folder 9, Box 149)
  - Willis [Edwin E.] speeches Mimeo, C.R., etc., 1963-1968 (Folder 1, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1953-1966 (Folder 2, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1953-1966 (Folder 3, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1957-1967 (Folder 4, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1964 (Folder 5, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1955-1967 (Folder 6, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1955-1967 (Folder 7, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1959-1966 (Folder 8, Box 150)
  - Edwin E. Willis, 1959-1966 (Folder 9, Box 150)
  - Willy Brandt - Guenther Guillaume (agents of influence), 1960-1993 (Folder 10, Box 150)
  - Wiretapping - basics, 1974 (Folder 1, Box 151)
    House Un-American Activities Committee, McNamara, Notes
  - Wiretapping - The Case for Bugging, September 7, 1968 (Folder 2, Box 151)
    Hal Lipset, "Ramparts"
  - Wiretapping News Clippings, 1971-1985 (Folder 3, Box 151)
  - Wiretapping Newsclippings, 1973-1988 (Folder 4, Box 151)
  - Wiretapping - A Paranoid's Guide to Bugging, September 7, 1988 (Folder 5, Box 151)
    "Ramparts"
  - Wiretapping Notes, 1971 (Folder 6, Box 151)
    McNamara, Notes
  - Wiretapping Notes, 1974 (Folder 7, Box 151)
  - Wiretapping - "Ivanov-Butchko-Alderman", 1968-1974 (Folder 8, Box 151)
    Espionage, Supreme Court, Trials
  - Wiretapping - "Wiretap - CT. Decisions" [U.S House of Representatives Envelope], 1969-1979 (Folder 9, Box 151)
    Supreme Court, United States Court of Appeals
  - Wiretapping - "Taps-Numbers" [United States Senate Envelope], 1972-1976 (Folder 10, Box 151)
    Interception of Wiretapping, Reports, United States Court of Appeals
  - Wiretapping - V.F.W Magazine, December 1960 (Folder 11, Box 151)
    V.F.W. Magazine
  - Wiretapping - Letter to Kathleen Wick, March 26, 1971 (Folder 12, Box 151)
    Correspondence, McNamara
  - Wiretapping - "The Wiretappers - The Reporter", 1955 (Folder 13, Box 151)
    Investigative Journalism
  - Wiretapping - Department of Justice - statement of Henry E. Peterson, 1974 (Folder 14, Box 151)
    Department of Justice, Wiretapping and Electronic Surveillance
  - Wiretapping - "Ma Bell Fights Off Invasion of her Domain" - article, 1978 (Folder 15, Box 151)
    American Telegraph and Telephone Company
  - Wiretapping - "Illinois Bell devises versatile new subscriber usage measuring system", 1974 (Folder 16, Box 151)
    Electronic Surveillance
  - Wiretapping - "Statement of William D. Ruckelshaus", May 9, 1974 (Folder 17, Box 151)
    Electronic Surveillance, Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights, Wiretapping
  - Wiretapping - Search-Query - 00048 Privacy report, 1975 (Folder 18, Box 151)
    Congressional Database Search Query Results
  - Wiretapping - Notes - misc., 1974-1976 (Folder 19, Box 151)